Uploaded by: Somnath Yadav follow on Instagram @somnath66
Despite appearances, I think you'll
find the city's on the rise.
Perhaps we should take shelter.
The city's on the rise?
Meereen is strong.
Commerce has returned to the markets.
The people are behind you.
Well, not all the people, of course.
No ruler that ever lived had
the support of all the people.
But the rebirth of Meereen is
the cause of this violence.
The Masters cannot let Meereen succeed.
Because if Meereen succeeds,
a city without slavery,
a city without Masters...
...it proves that no one needs a Master.
Good.
Shall we begin?
Do we have a plan?
I will crucify the Masters.
I will set their fleets afire,
kill every last one of their soldiers,
and return their cities to the dirt.
That is my plan.
You don't approve?
You once told me you knew
what your father was.
Did you know his plans
for King's Landing
when the Lannister armies
were at his gates?
Probably not.
Well, he told my brother
and Jaime told me.
He had caches of wildfire
hidden under the Red Keep,
the Guildhalls, the Sept of Baelor,
all the major thoroughfares.
He would have burned every
one of his citizens.
The loyal ones and the traitors.
Every man, woman, and child.
That's why Jaime killed him.
This is entirely different.
You're talking about destroying cities.
It's not entirely different.
I'd like to suggest an
alternate approach.
Once before, I offered you peace.
If you had not been so arrogant,
you could have returned to your
homeland with a fleet of ships.
Instead, you will flee
Slaver's Bay on foot
like the beggar queen you are.
We are here to discuss
terms of surrender,
not to trade insults.
The terms are simple.
You and your foreign friends will abandon
the Great Pyramid and the city of Meereen.
The Unsullied you stole
from Kraznys mo Nakloz
will remain to be sold again
to the highest bidder.
The translator you stole from
Kraznys mo Nakloz will remain
to be sold again to the highest bidder.
The dragons beneath the Great
Pyramid will be slaughtered.
We obviously didn't communicate clearly.
We're here to discuss
your surrender, not mine.
I imagine it's difficult
adjusting to the new reality.
Your reign is over.
My reign has just begun.
Dracarys.
Your men have a choice:
fight and die for masters who would
never fight and die for you,
or go home to your families.
Thank you for the armada.
Our queen does love ships.
Now, last time we spoke, we made a pact.
You violated that pact.
You declared war upon us.
Though our queen does
have a forgiving nature,
this cannot be forgiven.
Our queen insists that
one of you must die
as punishment for your crimes.
It always seems a bit
abstract, doesn't it,
other people dying?
Him. He should die.
Yes, him. He's not one of us.
He's an outsider, a lowborn.
He does not speak for us.
Please.
Tell your people what happened here.
Tell them you live by the
grace of Her Majesty.
When they come forward with
notions of retribution
or ideas about returning the slave
cities to their former glory,
remind them what happened
when Daenerys Stormborn and
her dragons came to Meereen.
You don't have to be here.
Yes, I do.
My beloved wife.
I've missed you terribly.
Thank you for returning
Lady Bolton safely.
Now, dismount and kneel before me,
surrender your army and proclaim me the true
Lord of Winterfell and Warden of the North.
I will pardon you for
deserting the Night's Watch.
I will pardon these treasonous
lords for betraying my house.
Come, bastard,
you don't have the men, you
don't have the horses,
and you don't have Winterfell.
Why lead those poor
souls into slaughter?
There's no need for a battle.
Get off your horse and kneel.
I'm a man of mercy.
You're right.
There's no need for a battle.
Thousands of men don't need to die.
Only one of us.
Let's end this the old way.
You against me.
I keep hearing stories
about you, bastard.
The way people in the
North talk about you,
you're the greatest
swordsman who ever walked.
Maybe you are that good.
Maybe not.
I don't know if I'd beat you.
But I know that my army will beat yours.
I have 6,000 men.
You have, what, half that?
Not even?
Aye, you have the numbers.
Will your men want to fight for you
when they hear you
wouldn't fight for them?
He's good. Very good.
Tell me, will you let
your little brother die
because you're too proud to surrender?
How do we know you have him?
Now, if you want to save...
You're going to die
tomorrow, Lord Bolton.
Sleep well.
She's a fine woman, your sister.
I look forward to having
her back in my bed.
And you're all fine-looking men.
My dogs are desperate to meet you.
I haven't fed them for
seven days. They're ravenous.
I wonder which parts they'll try first.
Your eyes?
Your balls?
We'll find out soon enough.
In the morning, then, bastard.
If he was smart, he'd stay inside
the walls of Winterfell and wait us out.
That's not his way. He knows
the North is watching.
If the other houses sense
weakness on his part,
they'll stop fearing him.
He can't have that. Fear is his power.
It's his weakness, too. His men
don't want to fight for him.
They're forced to fight for him.
If they feel the tide turning...
It's not his men that worry me.
It's his horses.
I know what mounted
knights can do to us.
You and Stannis cut through
us like piss through snow.
We're digging trenches
all along our flanks.
They won't be able to hit us
the way that Stannis hit you,
in a double envelopment.
A pincer move.
They won't be able to
hit us from the sides.
Good.
It's crucial that we
let them charge at us.
They've got the numbers,
we need the patience.
If we let him buckle our
center, he'll pursue.
Then we'll have him
surrounded on three sides.
Did you really think that cunt
would fight you man-to-man?
No.
But I wanted to make him angry.
I want him coming at us full tilt.
We should all get some sleep.
Rest, Jon Snow. We need
you sharp tomorrow.
So you've met the enemy,
drawn up your battle plans.
Aye, for what they're worth.
You've known him for the space
of a single conversation,
you and your trusted advisors,
and you sit around making your plans
on how to defeat a man you don't know.
I lived with him.
I know the way his mind works.
I know how he likes to hurt people.
Did it ever once occur to you
that I might have some insight?
You're right.
You think he's going to
fall into your trap.
He won't. He's the one who lays traps.
- He's overconfident.
- He plays with people.
He's far better at it than you.
He's been doing it all his life.
Aye, and what have I been doing all
my life? Playing with broomsticks?
I fought beyond the Wall against
worse than Ramsay Bolton.
I've defended the Wall from
You don't know him.
All right, tell me.
What should we do? How
do we get Rickon back?
We'll never get him back.
Rickon is Ned Stark's trueborn son,
which makes him a greater
threat to Ramsay
than you, a bastard, or me, a girl.
As long as he lives, Ramsay's claim
to Winterfell will be contested,
which means he won't live long.
We can't give up on our brother.
Listen to me, please. He
wants you to make a mistake.
Of course he does. What
should I do differently?
I don't know! I don't know
anything about battles.
Just don't do what he wants you to do.
Aye, that's good advice.
You think that's obvious?
Well, it is a bit obvious.
If you had asked for my advice earlier,
I would have told you not
to attack Winterfell
until we had a larger force,
or is that obvious, too?
When will we have a larger force?!
We've pleaded with every
house that'll have us.
The Blackfish can't help us.
We're lucky to have this many men.
- It's not enough! - No, it's
not enough. It's what we have!
Battles have been won
against greater odds.
If Ramsay wins,
I'm not going back there alive.
Do you understand me?
I won't let ever let
him touch you again.
I'll protect you, I promise.
No one can protect me.
No one can protect anyone.
You think there's hope?
I've never seen these
Bolton fuckers fight.
And they've never seen
the free folk fight,
so, yes, there's hope.
You want to avenge your king, don't you?
It wasn't the Boltons defeated Stannis.
It was Stannis himself.
I loved the man.
He lifted me up and made me something.
But he had demons in his skull
whispering foul things.
- You saw these demons?
- What?
No, it's a manner of speaking.
Not... actual demons.
Well, you loved that cunt Stannis
and I loved the man he burned.
Mance didn't have demons in his skull.
He didn't torch people or
listen to some red witch.
I believed in him.
I thought he was the man to
lead us through the Long Night.
But I was wrong just like you.
Maybe that was our mistake,
believing in kings.
Jon Snow's not a king.
No, he's not.
I need a good drink to help me
sleep the night before a fight.
You want some?
I have a jug of sour goat's milk
stronger than any of that grape water
you southern twats like sucking on.
No, thanks. It does sound delicious,
but I better keep a clear head.
I can never sleep the
night before a battle.
So what do you do all night?
I walk.
Think and walk.
Think and walk until I'm
far enough away from camp
that no one can hear me
shitting my guts out.
Happy shitting.
My lady.
You weren't at the war council.
I'm not a soldier.
Any advice?
Don't lose.
If I do, if I fall...
don't bring me back.
I'll have to try.
I'm ordering you not to bring me back.
I am not your servant, Jon Snow.
You're in my camp. I'm the commander.
I serve the Lord of Light.
I do what he commands.
How do you know what he commands?
I interpret his signs...
as well as I can.
If the Lord didn't want
me to bring you back,
how did I bring you back?
I have no power.
Only what he gives me
and he gave me you.
Why?
I don't know.
Maybe you're only needed for this small
part of his plan and nothing else.
Maybe he brought you here to die again.
What kind of god would
do something like that?
The one we've got.
Game of Thrones 6x09 - The Battle of Bastards.
Last time we saw each other
was at Winterfell, yes?
You were making jokes about
my height, I seem to recall.
Everyone who makes a joke
about a dwarf's height
thinks he's the only person ever to
make a joke about a dwarf's height.
"The height of nobility,"
"a man of your stature,"
"someone to look up to."
You're all making the
same five or six jokes.
- It was a long time ago.
- It was.
And how have things been
going for you since then?
Not so well, I gather.
Can't imagine you would have murdered the
Stark boys if things had been going well.
I didn't murder the Stark boys.
But I did things that were
just as bad or worse.
And he paid for them.
Doesn't seem like it.
He's still alive.
It was complicated for you, I'm sure,
growing up at Winterfell.
Never quite knowing who you were.
But then, we all live
complicated lives, don't we?
You've brought us 100
ships from the Iron Fleet
with men to sail them.
In return, I expect you
want me to support
your claim to the throne
of the Iron Islands?
Not my claim. Hers.
And what's wrong with you?
I'm not fit to rule.
We can agree upon that at least.
Has the Iron Islands
ever had a queen before?
No more than Westeros.
Our Uncle Euron returned
home after a long absence.
He murdered our father and took
the Salt Throne from Yara.
He would have murdered
us if we'd stayed.
Lord Tyrion tells me your
father was a terrible king.
You and I have that in common.
We do.
And both murdered by a usurper as well.
Will their ships be enough?
With the former Masters'
fleet, possibly.
Barely.
There are more than 100
ships in the Iron Fleet.
There are and Euron is building more.
He's going to offer them to you.
So why shouldn't I wait for him?
The Iron Fleet isn't all he's bringing.
He also wants to give you...
His big cock, I think he said.
Euron's offer is also an
offer of marriage, you see.
You won't get one without the other.
And I imagine your offer is
free of any marriage demands?
I never demand, but I'm
up for anything, really.
He murdered our father and
would have murdered us.
He'll murder you as soon
as you have what he wants.
The Seven Kingdoms.
All of them.
And you don't want the Seven Kingdoms?
Your ancestors defeated ours
and took the Iron Islands.
We ask you to give them back.
And that's all?
We'd like you to help us
murder an uncle or two
who don't think a woman's fit to rule.
Reasonable.
What if everyone starts
demanding their independence?
She's not demanding, she's asking.
The others are free to ask as well.
Our fathers were evil
men, all of us here.
They left the world worse
than they found it.
We're not going to do that.
We're going to leave the world
better than we found it.
You will support my claim as
queen of the Seven Kingdoms
and respect the integrity
of the Seven Kingdoms.
No more reaving, roving,
raiding, or raping.
That's our way of life.
No more.
Do you like games, little man?
Let's play a game.
Run to your brother.
The sooner you make it to him,
the sooner you get to see him again.
That's it.
That's the game.
Easy.
Ready?
Go.
No, you have to run, remember?
Those are the rules.
`T`U`S`U`B`T`I`T`U`L`O`C`O`M
Don't.
Prepare to charge.
Prepare to charge!
- Draw!
Draw!
Loose!
Go! Go! Follow your commander!
Run and fight!
Nock!
- Draw!
- Loose!
Now.
Cavalry, charge!
- Nock!
- Draw!
We'll just kill our own men. Stand down.
- Loose!
Get word...
No!
Loose!
- Loose!
We may as well be
taking shits back here.
Follow!
It's time, go.
- Who owns the North?
- We do!
Show me!
Hey!
Infantry, advance!
With me, lads! Break their line!
Help me!
- Tormund!
- Get him back!
Infantry, advance.
Both sides!
Fall back!
Fuck this, come on!
We're going home!
Open the gate!
Archers to the wall.
- Their army's gone.
- Our army's gone.
We have Winterfell.
They don't have the men for a siege.
All we have to do is wait.
Archers!
To the wall!
You suggested one-on-one
combat, didn't you?
I've reconsidered.
I think that sounds
like a wonderful idea.
We're going to bury my
brother in the crypt
next to my father.
Jon.
Where is he?
Sansa.
Hello, Sansa.
Is this where I'll be staying now?
No.
Our time together is
about to come to an end.
That's all right.
You can't kill me.
I'm part of you now.
Your words will disappear.
Your house will disappear.
Your name will disappear.
All memory of you will disappear.
My hounds will never harm me.
You haven't fed them in seven days.
You said it yourself.
They're loyal beasts.
They were.
Now they're starving.
Sit.
Down.
Down!
Down! Down!
uploaded by: Somnath Yadav follow on instagram @somnath66